fashionbombdaily.com 2013-11-26

# Privacy Policy | The Fashion Bomb Blog : Celebrity Fashion, Fashion News, What To Wear, Runway Show ReviewsThe Fashion Bomb Blog : Celebrity Fashion, Fashion News, What To Wear, Runway Show Reviews

Privacy Policy

At The Fashion Bomb, we are committed to protecting the privacy of our users and visitors. The following Privacy Policy outlines the information The Fashion Bomb, LLC. (The Fashion Bomb) may collect and how we may use that information to better serve visitors and members of The Fashion Bomb.

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at thefashionbomb@gmail.com.

1\. Children Under the Age of 13

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, The Fashion Bomb does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the The Fashion Bomb from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the The Fashion Bomb at any time or in any manner. If The Fashion Bomb learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on The Fashion Bomb without verified parental consent, then The Fashion Bomb will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

2\. Information We Collect

* Information Submitted by a user. The Fashion Bomb collects personal information when you register or request information from us. The personal information we collect is listed below:

o Login Name

o Password

o Email address

o Name

o Postal Code

* You may also submit information about other people. For example, you may enter a friend’s email to invite to The Fashion Bomb, or email links to The Fashion Bomb. In this circumstance, we collect the following information about the recipient:

o Email address

* Non-submitted Information Collected. The Fashion Bomb may also collect non-personal information not associated with your identity. We collect this data to improve The Fashion Bomb. The non-submitted information we collect is listed below:

o IP

o Time

o File

o Data transferred

o Browser type and version

o Operating system

o Cookies

3\. How We Use Your Information

Among our primary goals in collecting information is to provide you with a customized experience when visiting our site and to make our site more valuable to you. We use this information to closely monitor which areas of the site are used most and to determine which areas we need to focus on improving. This information is used exclusively by The Fashion Bomb in aggregate form so that we may continue to improve the value of the services and information on The Fashion Bomb for our members as a whole.

As a valued customer of The Fashion Bomb, we will occasionally contact you, typically by e-mail (or any other way you prefer) in order to notify you of special promotions, and up-to-date news, custom-tailored to your personal interests. Of course, if you do not wish to receive this personalized information, you can remove yourself from receiving such information by changing the appropriate option on your user account.

The Fashion Bomb uses your Internet Protocol (IP) address to help diagnose problems with our computer server, and to administer our web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you, and to gather broad demographic data. Your IP address contains no personal information about you.

Please note that, once you’ve logged on to our servers, we use cookies keep track of your application states and log in status. Cookies are small files that take up minimal room on your computer and cannot, by itself, damage your computer’s files. Cookies work by assigning a number to a user that has no meaning outside of the assigning web site, in this case, The Fashion Bomb. If you do not want information to be collected through the use of cookies, your browser allows you to deny or accept the use of cookies. There may, however, be some features on The Fashion Bomb„ which requires the use of cookies in order to customize the delivery of information and content to you.

Except as described above, we will not monitor, edit or disclose any personal information about you or your account, without your prior consent unless we have a belief that such action is necessary to: (i) comply with legal process or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of The Fashion Bomb; (iii) enforce our Terms of Service; (iv) protect the interests of users of our services other than you or any other person; or (v) operate or conduct maintenance and repair of The Fashion Bomb’s services or equipment as authorized by law.

4\. Our Disclosure of Your Information

The Fashion Bomb does not sell or rent personal information about its customers to any third parties at this time. In the event The Fashion Bomb does engage in such commerce in the future, you will have an opportunity to remove yourself from any such lists prior to your inclusion therein by emailing us at thefashionbomb@gmail.com or by changing the appropriate option on your user account. The Fashion Bomb does, however, perform statistical analysis of customer usage in order to measure interest in, and use of, the various parts of The Fashion Bomb, and The Fashion Bomb shares that information with current and prospective advertisers, and other interested third parties. But, this information is aggregated data only (statistics, etc.), and contains no personally identifiable information whatsoever.

The Fashion Bomb cooperates with all law enforcement inquires and with all third parties to enforce their intellectual property or other rights.

You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personal information in chat areas, on bulletin boards, or in classified areas within The Fashion Bomb, that information might be collected and disseminated by third-parties, and result in, among other things, unsolicited inquiries, messages, and offers from third-parties. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and this third-party conduct is out of the control of The Fashion Bomb. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

The Fashion Bomb also contains links to other web sites. The Fashion Bomb is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
5\. Security

The personally identifiable information we collect is securely stored within our database, and we use standard, industry-wide practices such as encryption, firewalls and (in some certain areas) SSL (Secure Socket Layers) for protecting your information. However, as effective as encryption technology is, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. We recommend that you not disclose your password to anyone.

6\. Revisions and Amendments

If you have further privacy concerns please do not hesitate to ask us by contacting thefashionbomb@gmail.com. This Privacy Policy is effective as of June 24, 2008. This Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party. The Fashion Bomb reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, modify, change or update this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update or modification on www.FashionBombDaily.com. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on The Fashion Bomb.

Be Sociable, Share!

  *
